<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>My Journal</title>
    <link href="https://ap-9512.github.io/gh-pages/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://ap-9512.github.io/gh-pages" />
    <updated>1970-01-01T05:30:00+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AP</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://ap-9512.github.io/gh-pages</id>

    <entry>
        <title>My First Post</title>
        <author>
            <name>AP</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ap-9512.github.io/gh-pages/my-first-post.html"/>
        <id>https://ap-9512.github.io/gh-pages/my-first-post.html</id>

        <updated>2020-07-15T09:16:49+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Alright, this will be a test post for my journal, which probably will be a voice recorded one so as to save time. I also think it will help me to improve my speaking skills. As this is an anonymous website, I will be true&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Alright, this will be a test post for my journal, which probably will be a voice recorded one so as to save time. I also think it will help me to improve my speaking skills.</p>
<p>As this is an anonymous website, I will be true to the best of my <em>"conscience".</em></p>
<p>Okay let's have a head-start. </p>
<p>If I feel like editing this one, then I will add a new post, as internet is unlimited.</p>
<p>Actually in the past I used to write all my entries on a wordpress blog, but now as the files I will upload will be audio files and the size is limited on wordpress to approx 5GB, I have thought of this. And of course, wordpress website that I created is not published and it has my name. So for now, till I achieve my greatness I cannot publish that website and also this website will be search engine <em>"unfriendly!!</em>😉<em>"</em></p>
<p>May God bless me with this activity, help me with this activity.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
